fxclub.com 2011-12-23

# Privacy Policy

**FOREX CLUB LLC  
PRIVACY POLICY**

**Your Privacy is Our Priority**

**Forex Club LLC** is committed to safeguarding all personal information that you provide us. This Privacy Policy describes how we handle and protect personal information we collect about individuals who apply for or receive our products and services. The provisions of this notice apply to former as well as current customers.

**Why and How We Collect Personal Information** When you apply for or maintain an account with Forex Club LLC, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. The personal information we collect about you includes:

  * information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, address, date of birth, social security number, occupation, assets and income;
  * information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates;
  * information we receive from consumer reporting agencies, such as your credit history and creditworthiness, and other entities not affiliated with Forex Club LLC; and
  * information you provide to us to verify your identity, such as a passport, or received from other entities not affiliated with Forex Club LLC.

**How We Protect Personal Information** We limit access to your personal information to those employees who need to know in order to conduct our business, service your account, and help you accomplish your financial objectives, such as providing you with a broad range of products and services. Our employees are required to maintain and protect the confidentiality of your personal information and must follow established procedures to do so. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. We do not rent or sell your name or personal information to anyone.

**Sharing Information with Our Affiliates** We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, and as permitted by applicable law. The information we share with affiliates for marketing purposes may include the information described above, such as name, address and account information, but will not include other credit information, such as credit history appearing on a consumer credit report or net worth and income information appearing on applications for our products and services.

**Disclosure to Non-Affiliated Third Parties** In order to support the financial products and services we provide to you, we may share the personal information described above with third party service providers and joint marketers not affiliated with us, including:

  * financial service institutions (e.g., advisers, dealers, brokers, trust companies and banks) with whom we have joint marketing agreements, such as agreements to market financial services or products that we jointly offer, endorse or sponsor; and
  * companies under contract to perform services for us or on our behalf such as vendors that prepare and mail statements and transaction confirmations or provide data processing, computer software maintenance and development, transaction 120 Wall Street, 16th Floor, New York, NEW YORK, NY 10005, UNITED STATES +1 (800) 881-3809, email: [info@fxclub.com](mailto:info@fxclub.com) processing and marketing services. These companies acting on our behalf are

required to keep your personal information confidential. Also, we may disclose personal information with non-affiliated companies and regulatory authorities as permitted or required by applicable law. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose unless we describe how such information will be used at

the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission to do so. 

**Accessing and Revisiting Your Personal Information** We endeavor to keep our customer files complete and accurate. We will give you reasonable access to the information we have about you. Most of this information is contained in account statements that you receive from us and applications that you submit to obtain our products and services. We encourage you to review this information and notify us if you believe any information should be corrected or updated. If you have a question or concern about your personal information or this privacy notice, please contact your account representative. If you would like to opt-out of receiving future emails, please unsubscribe by clicking the Remove link at the footer of each email.  

**Background** **Affiliation Status Information Center** **(BASIC)** One of the first things any investor should do before trading in FX products is conduct a background check on the firms and individuals offering these products. It is also a very good idea to routinely perform a background check on the firms and individuals offering these products. National Futures Association ("NFA") maintains a database of futures-related information, including Commodity Futures Trading Commission ("CFTC") registration information, NFA membership information, regulatory actions and information concerning certain types of customer claims. The CFTC registration and NFA membership information provided in the system called Background affiliation Status Information System, or "BASIC" includes the current and historical CFTC registration and NFA membership statuses of individuals and firms. The regulatory information available in BASIC includes actions taken by NFA's Committees, by the CFTC and by U.S. futures exchanges.

Using NFA's Background Affiliation Status Information Center (BASIC), investors can quickly and easily check the registration status and disciplinary history of every firm and individual conducting FX business with the retail public. To access the BASIC system, you can do so by going to <http://www.nfa.futures.org/basicnet>
